http://www.computercablestore.com/privacy-policy

Help
Contact us Mon-Fri 8:30am-5pm EST.
Wishlist
(0)
0
Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Computer Cable Store
Categories
shop by brand
shop by savings
Welcome, Please Sign In!
Solder Type D-Sub Connectors
Hoods (Back Shells)
Privacy policy
This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) sets forth  ComputerCableStore.com (“ComputerCableStore.com”) policies regarding the collection and use of information relating to the ComputerCableStore.com Web site (the “Web Site”) accessible for use by users who visit the Web Site (“Visitors”).
INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
GeneralVisitors understand and agree that ComputerCableStore.com may collect, maintain, and process information provided by such parties to ComputerCableStore.com, and specifically, product warranty information collected by ComputerCableStore.com, concerning such Visitors, and their purchases, on and through the Web Site. Visitors represent and warrant that all information they provide to ComputerCableStore.com. is true, accurate, current, non-misleading, and consistent and relevant for the purpose for which such information is provided.
Public Areas of the Web SiteVisitors may visit areas of the Web Site without disclosing any personal information about themselves. However, Visitors will have the opportunity to send information to ComputerCableStore.com to register product for warranty, and to request to receive information from ComputerCableStore.com, in which case an e-mail, address or other information may be required in order to allow ComputerCableStore.com to comply with the request, and for other purposes as may be disclosed at the time the request is made. Visitors may elect to opt-out from receiving materials from ComputerCableStore.com by following the instructions in OPT-OUT CHOICES below. ComputerCableStore.com will not request more information than is reasonably necessary to provide requested services.
Collected InformationIn order to participate in the Warranty Services, or any other such services offered, ComputerCableStore.com. requires Visitors to provide certain contact and other information (“Information”) ComputerCableStore.com may also use Information to communicate with Visitors regarding available features and other activities relating to the Web Site and the Services. ComputerCableStore.com may also use Information to send Visitors information about products or services available on or through ComputerCableStore.com and offers made available by other entities, which may be sent by ComputerCableStore.com or the entity making the offer. Instructions on how to request no future communications from ComputerCableStore.com or not have ComputerCableStore.com share Information with unaffiliated third parties, are set forth in OPT-OUT CHOICES below.
Protecting Your Children’s Information PrivacyWe do not knowingly solicit or collect data from children, and we do not knowingly market to children online without express parental consent or notification. If we knowingly receive online information from any child we will only use the information to respond directly to a child’s request. We recognize that protecting children’s identities and online privacy is important and that responsibility rests with us and with parents. If you believe your child has provided personally identifiable information to us, please contact us so we can allow you the opportunity to review and delete such information.
Usage DataComputerCableStore.com may record and collect information about how Visitors use the Web Site. This data may include a Visitor’s domain name, language, type of browser and operating system, Internet Service Provider, Internet protocol (IP) address, the Web site from which they arrived at the Web Site, and the amount of time spent on the Web Site or using the Exchange (collectively, “Usage Data”). ComputerCableStore.com will monitor and use Usage Data to measure the Web Site’s performance and Exchange activity and improve the Web Site’s design and functionality. ComputerCableStore.com may also use Usage Data to develop and distribute to third parties statistical and general information about how the Web Site is used.
CookiesAs with many state-of-the-art Internet sites, ComputerCableStore.com uses “cookies” to, among other things, enhance the functionality of the Web Site and to make transactions and other activities through the Web Site more convenient and efficient for Visitors. A “cookie” is a file stored locally on a user’s computer. Most Internet browsers include preference settings that allow users to be notified and control whether cookies are transferred to their computers.
OPT-OUT CHOICES
To “opt-out” of (1) any consents previously given to ComputerCableStore.com, (2) receiving communications from ComputerCableStore.com., or (3) having contact information disclosed to third parties , send an e-mail to CustomerService@ComputerCableStore.com with “Unsubscribe” or “Do Not Share” in the subject line. Notwithstanding this right to request to cease receiving communications from ComputerCableStore.com and have ComputerCableStore.com not share contact information with third parties, ComputerCableStore.com retains the right to collect, maintain and process information provided by and collected about Visitors on and through the Web Site, and disclose such information to comply with its reasonable business and legal obligations.
ACCESS TO PERSONAL INFORMATION
To the extent that Visitors may provide personal information to ComputerCableStore.com on or through the Web Site, ComputerCableStore.com will allow reasonable access to, and review of, such information, where such information is readily available, upon proper verification of the person seeking such access and review. Requests for revisions to personal information may be made to ComputerCableStore.com through CustomerService@ComputerCableStore.com.
LINKED SITES
ComputerCableStore.com may provide links to third parties’ Web sites (“Linked Sites”) from the Site or the Exchange. Linked Sites are not reviewed, controlled or examined by ComputerCableStore.com in any way and ComputerCableStore.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any such Linked Sites, or any additional links contained therein. These links do not imply ComputerCableStore.com endorsement of or association with the Linked Sites.
DISCLOSURE PURSUANT TO LAW
ComputerCableStore.com may make information concerning the Web Site, and the uses thereof, available to law enforcement personnel and agencies when requested to do so or as required by law. ComputerCableStore.com may also disclose such information upon a good faith belief that it is required to do so, in order to protect its property or in furtherance to an investigation regarding a breach of the Terms of Use.
CONSENT TO PROCESSING
By using or providing information to the Web Site, Visitors understand and unambiguously consent to the collection, processing and use of such information in the United States and other countries and territories for the purposes set forth in this Policy.
SERVICES PROVIDERS
ComputerCableStore.com may utilize the services of unaffiliated service providers to provide or perform certain services and functions on the Web Site. For example, ComputerCableStore.com may use a Web site tracking evaluation firm to analyze use of the Web Site. ComputerCableStore.com will make information concerning use of the Web Site available to these service providers, as necessary to perform these functions. Any access to such information will be limited to the purpose for which such information was provided to the service provider.
TRANSFER OF INFORMATION
Information provided by or collected about Visitors may be sold, assigned, or transferred to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, dissolution, or sale or transfer of the substantial assets of ComputerCableStore.com.
SECURITY
ComputerCableStore.com takes seriously the security of information related to the use of the Web Site and has implemented adequate systems and procedures intended to reduce the risk of unauthorized access to such information. However, due to the nature of the Internet as an open communication medium, ComputerCableStore.com cannot guarantee that communications with the Web Site will be free from unauthorized access.
UPDATES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY
ComputerCableStore.com may, in its sole discretion, update this Policy at any time and from time to time, by posting the amended Policy on the Web Site. The revised or amended Policy shall automatically be effective after it is initially posted on the Web Site. Any access to or use of the Web Site following such update shall be deemed consent to such update. Visitors are therefore encouraged to refer back to this page regularly. This Policy may not be otherwise amended without the written consent of ComputerCableStore.com.
USER COMMENTS, FEEDBACK AND OTHER SUBMISSIONS
If, at our request, you send certain specific submissions (for example contest entries) or without a request from us you send creative ideas, suggestions, proposals, plans, or other materials, whether online, by email, by postal mail, or otherwise (collectively, 'comments'), you agree that we may, at any time, without restriction, edit, copy, publish, distribute, translate and otherwise use in any medium any comments that you forward to us. We are and shall be under no obligation (1) to maintain any comments in confidence; (2) to pay compensation for any comments; or (3) to respond to any comments.
We may, but have no obligation to, monitor, edit or remove content that we determine in our sole discretion are unlawful, offensive, threatening, libelous, defamatory, pornographic, obscene or otherwise objectionable or violates any party’s intellectual property or these Terms of Service.
You agree that your comments will not violate any right of any third-party, including copyright, trademark, privacy, personality or other personal or proprietary right. You further agree that your comments will not contain libelous or otherwise unlawful, abusive or obscene material, or contain any computer virus or other malware that could in any way affect the operation of the Service or any related website. You may not use a false e-mail address, pretend to be someone other than yourself, or otherwise mislead us or third-parties as to the origin of any comments. You are solely responsible for any comments you make and their accuracy. We take no responsibility and assume no liability for any comments posted by you or any third-party.
CONTACT, QUESTIONS, COMMENTS, COMPLAINTS
If you would like to communicate with ComputerCableStore.com or have questions, comments or complaints about this Policy, or the Web Site, please forward such communication to:
Data ControllerComputerCableStore.com.
Copyright © 2020 Computer Cable Store. All rights reserved.
